Finding Aid of the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology Records, 1923-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology Records, 1923-2015
American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology
UWM Manuscript Collection 139
Accession 2011-011
Accession 2013-038
Accession 2015-035
259.7 cubic ft. (510 boxes) 40 binders 1 oversize folder 30,895 digital files (79.5 GB) 1 film reel 4 safety film negatives plus additions of 6 cubic ft. (6 boxes)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Records of a Milwaukee-based professional medical organization. Formed in 1943 from the merger of the Society for the Study of Asthma and Allied Conditions and the American Association for the Study of Allergy, the organization was originally named the American Academy of Allergy (AAA); in 1982 the name changed to the American Academy of Allergy & Immunology (AAAI); the current name, the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma and Immunology (AAAAI) was adopted in 1995. Records exist in the collection from the two predecessor organizations, though the bulk of the materials, including photographs and textual records, are from the AAA, the AAAI and the AAAAI.
The American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology was formed by the merger of the American Association for the Study of Allergy and the Association for the Study of Asthma and Allied Conditions. A group of West Coast and Midwest physicians formed the American Association for the Study of Allergy in 1923 and the group became known as the Western Society. In 1924, New York physicians interested in allergy met and formed the Society for the Study of Asthma and Allied Conditions; this group became known as the Eastern Society. When the Western and Eastern Societies merged in December 1943, the new association was named the American Academy of Allergy. The executive office was established in Milwaukee in 1948. In 1982, the name was changed to the American Academy of Allergy and Immunology and in 1995 to the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology.
Scope and content notes of each series are provided in the contents list.
This collection was received in, and is organized in, multiple parts. Additional materials have not been physically or intellectually arranged and interfiled, and researchers may need to consult more than one part of the collection to locate similar materials.
The records are arranged into the following series:
Executive Committee and Board of Directors
Annual Meetings
Annual Meeting Handouts
Newsletters and Publications
Committees, Council, and Interest Sections
Related Organizations
Member Files
Audio-Visual Materials
Videocassettes and Film
Audio Cassettes and Digital Audio Files
Photographs
Continuing Medical Education
Patient and Public Education
Administrative Files
Associates to the AAAAI
Oral History Interviews of the Oral History Project for the AAAAI
Historical Material
Artifacts from the History of Asthma Treatment
Memorabilia
Within series 7, audio cassettes are housed in boxes 391-403, 497, 523, 528-531, and 542. Videocassettes are housed in boxes 408-414 and 497. Photographs are housed in boxes 330-334, 430, and 441
The collection contains additional accessions.
Accession 2011-011: Additions, 1988-2010
Accession 2013-038: Publications and Annual Meeting Materials, 1997-2013
Accession 2015-035: Publications and Other Additions, 1995-2015
Finding aid for accession 2015-035 available in the Archives.
Administrative/Restriction Information
Restrictions on access are noted in the contents lists. If no restrictions are noted, the materials are open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
The agreement between the AAAAI and UWM was executed in October 1998. Due to the high number of accessions received by the Archives Department on a regular basis, detailed information about accessions is not given on this finding aid but is available upon request.
As of January 2017 electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core i5-4570 CPU (3.20 GHz, 4 GB RAM) running Windows 7, with Service Pack 1. Major exceptions for accessible files are some of the programs used to provide embedded access to poster abstracts and educational programs, many of which were designed for Windows 3.1 or earlier and do not function properly on modern systems. The Archives has made the PDFs of the abstracts and articles themselves available where possible in these cases. The software is being preserved in binary format in the event that the Archives acquires the technology to make this software usable. Software used to access the files includes Windows Picture and Fax Viewer, Google Chrome, Windows Media Player, Adobe Reader XI, and Microsoft Office Suite 2007.
The collection includes records in the following file formats:
Windows Media Audio [.wma]
Acrobat PDF 1.3-1.6 - Portable Document Format [.pdf]
Microsoft Word Document 97-2003 [.doc]
Waveform Audio [.wav]
Microsoft Excel 97 Workbook [.xls]
Portable Network Graphics 1.0 [.png]
MPEG 1/2 Audio Layer 3 [.mp3]
Graphics Interchange Format 87a-89a [.gif]
JPEG File Interchange Format 1.01-1.02 [.jpg]
Adobe Flash 8 [.swf]
Hypertext Markup Language [.html]
Macromedia FLV [.flv]
Windows Portable Executable [.exe]
The executable files for the catalog abstracts must be run from the access CDs.
Contents List
- Records, 1923-2015, UWM Manuscript Collection 139; 257.9 cubic ft. (741 boxes) 40 binders 1 oversize folder 30,895 digital files (79.5 GB) 1 film reel 4 safety film negatives
  - 1. Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1944-2015
    This series is restricted.
    The bulk of this series consists of agenda books containing agendas of annual and interim meetings of the executive committee, reports by officers and committees, and minutes. Correspondence is included in this series, the bulk of which is between the executive committee and other committees. Correspondence files from past officers are also included.
    - Agenda Book
      Beginning with November 2005, Board of Directors Meeting Agenda and Division Agenda books are filed together.
      - 1948 April (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - 1950 March and September (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - 1956 February, June, and October (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - 1957 February (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - 1957 October (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - 1958 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - 1958 October (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - 1959 February (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1959 October (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - 1960 January (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - 1960 October (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - 1961 February (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - 1961 October (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 1962 February (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - 1962 October (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - 1963 March (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 1963 October (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - 1964 February (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - 1964 September (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - 1965 February (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - 1965 October (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - 1966 February (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - 1966 October (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - 1967 February (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - 1967 November (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1968 February (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - 1968 October (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
      - 1969 March (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
      - 1969 September (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
      - 1970 February (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
      - 1970 September (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - 1970 September (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - 1971 February (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - 1971 September (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - 1972 February (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - 1972 September (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - 1973 February (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - 1973 September (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - 1974 January (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - 1974 September (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - 1975 February (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - 1975 September (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - 1976 March (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - 1977 March (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - 1977 September (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - 1978 February (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - 1978 September (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - 1979 March (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - 1979 September (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - 1979 September (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - 1980 February (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
      - 1980 September (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
      - 1981 March (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
      - 1981 September (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
      - 1982 March (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
      - 1982 September (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
      - 1983 March (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
      - 1983 September (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
      - 1983 September (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
      - 1984 March (Box 9, Folder 3-6)
      - 1984 September (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
      - 1984 September (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
      - 1985 March (Box 10, Folder 5-8)
      - 1985 March (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
      - 1985 October (Box 11, Folder 3-7)
      - 1985 October (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - 1986 March (Box 12, Folder 2-5)
      - 1986 October (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - 1986 October (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
      - 1987 February (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
      - 1987 February (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      - 1987 July (Box 14, Folder 3-6)
      - 1987 November (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
      - 1988 March (Box 15, Folder 4-7)
      - 1988 July (Box 16, Folder 1-5)
      - 1988 November (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
      - 1988 November (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      - 1989 February (Box 17, Folder 3-6)
      - 1989 February Additions (Box 443, Folder 1)
      - 1989 July (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - 1989 July (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
      - 1989 October (Box 18, Folder 4-6)
      - 1990 March (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - 1990 March (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
      - 1990 July (Box 19, Folder 4-7)
      - 1990 November (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
      - 1991 March (Box 20, Folder 4-6)
      - 1991 June (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
      - 1991 November (Box 21, Folder 3-5)
      - 1992 March (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - 1992 March (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
      - 1992 June (Box 22, Folder 4-7)
      - 1992 June (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
      - 1992 November (Box 23, Folder 3-7)
      - 1993 March (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - 1993 March (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
      - 1993 June (Box 24, Folder 5-7)
      - 1993 June (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - 1993 November (Box 25, Folder 2-6)
      - 1994 March (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
      - 1994 March (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
      - 1994 June (Box 26, Folder 4-7)
      - 1994 June (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - 1994 November (Box 27, Folder 2-5)
      - 1995 February (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
      - 1995 February (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
      - 1995 July (Box 28, Folder 4-7)
      - 1995 December (Box 520, Folder 19-20)
      - 1996 March (Box 28, Folder 8-9)
      - 1996 March (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
      - 1996 June (Box 29, Folder 3-6)
      - 1996 November (Box 29, Folder 7-9)
      - 1997 February (Box 29, Folder 10-11)
      - 1997 February (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - 1997 June (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
      - 1997 November (Box 30, Folder 4-6)
      - 1998 March (Box 30, Folder 7-9)
      - 1998 June (Box 30, Folder 11-13)
      - 1998 November (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
      - 1999 February (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
      - 1999 June (Box 470, Folder 1-2)
      - 1999 August (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
      - 1999 November (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - 1999 November (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - 2000 March (Box 470, Folder 3-4)
      - 2000 June (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - 2000 November (Box 428, Folder 2-3)
      - 2000 November Additions (Box 428, Folder 4)
      - 2001 March (Box 443, Folder 2-4)
      - 2001 June (Box 443, Folder 5-6)
      - 2001 June Additions (Box 443, Folder 7)
      - 2001 November (Box 470, Folder 5-7)
      - 2002 March (Box 471, Folder 5-7)
      - 2002 June (Box 495, Folder 7)
      - 2002 November (Box 540, Folder 49-50)
      - 2003 March (Box 494, Folder 3)
      - 2003 May (Box 490, Folder 12)
      - 2003 November (Box 512, Folder 1-2)
      - 2004 March (Box 526, Folder 23-24)
      - 2004 June (Box 526, Folder 34-35)
      - 2004 November (Box 540, Folder 43-44)
      - 2005 March (Box 534, Folder 10)
      - 2005 June
        - Meeting Agenda (Box 540, Folder 51)
        - Division Agenda (Box 540, Folder 58)
      - 2005 November (Box 597, Folder 1-3)
      - 2006 March (Box 597, Folder 4-6)
      - 2006 June (Box 597, Folder 7-8)
      - 2007 February (Box 685, Folder 1-2)
      - 2007 June/July (Box 685, Folder 3-4)
      - 2007 November (Box 706, Folder 1-2)
      - 2008 March (Box 706, Folder 3-4)
      - 2008 June (Box 710, Folder 1-2)
      - 2008 November (Box 710, Folder 3-4)
      - 2009
        - Division Agenda (Box 720, Folder 1)
        - Meeting Agenda (Box 720, Folder 2)
    - Amalgamation, Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 443, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting Sites, Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Austen, K. Frank, President-Elect Files, 1980-1981 (Box 443, Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors, Candidates, 2008-2009 (Box 710, Folder 5-6)
    - Buckley, Rebecca, Presidential Files, 1978-1980 (Box 443, Folder 10)
    - Business Meeting, Slides, 1993-1995, Slides (35 mm) (Box 67, Folder 6-8)
    - Busse, William, Presidential Files, Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 534, Folder 50)
    - Cohen, Sheldon, Historian Files, 1950-1970 (Box 443, Folder 11-12)
    - Conference Calls, Agenda and Minutes
      - 1992-1993 February (Box 455, Folder 1-2)
      - 1993 July-October (Box 685, Folder 5-6)
      - 1993 (Box 388, Folder 1)
      - 1994 (Box 388, Folder 2-6)
      - 1994 (Box 389, Folder 1-3)
      - 1994 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
      - 1995 (Box 389, Folder 4)
      - 1995 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - 1995 January-December (Box 594, Folder 1-16)
      - 1996 January-June (Box 594, Folder 17-25)
      - 1996 July-December (Box 595, Folder 1-8)
      - 1997 January-December (Box 595, Folder 9-22)
      - 1998 January-December (Box 595, Folder 23-37)
      - 1999 January-December (Box 595, Folder 1-16)
    - Correspondence
      - 1964-1970 (Box 132, Folder 4)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 130, Folder 3)
      - 1974-1984 (Box 130, Folder 4-10)
      - 1985-1990 (Box 131, Folder 1-8)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 378, Folder 1-2)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 132, Folder 1-3)
      - 1992-1995 (Box 335, Folder 1-5)
      - 1995 (Box 378, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence to Board of Directors, 1996-1998 (Box 597, Folder 9-10)
    - Dworetzky, Murray
      - Amalgamation Correspondence, 1975 (Box 443, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1994 (Box 443, Folder 18)
      - 1969 Meeting Planning, Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 443, Folder 14)
      - Presidential Files, 1966-1969 (Box 443, Folder 15-17)
    - Election Ballot, 1994-1995, 1997-2003 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Executive Secretary Materials, 1956-1967 (Box 443, Folder 19)
    - Fall Leadership Development Retreat, 2002 (Box 517, Folder 31)
    - Farr, Richard, Presidential Files, 1968-1970 (Box 443, Folder 20-21)
    - Fink, Jordan
      - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 389, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence re: Clinical Ecology, 1984-1985 (Box 597, Folder 11)
    - Fireman, Philip, Presidential Files
      - Incoming Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 593, Folder 1-5)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 593, Folder 6-9)
    - Freedman, Samuel, Historian's File, 1976-1977 (Box 443, Folder 22)
    - Frick, Oscar, Presidential File, 1977-1979 (Box 443, Folder 23)
    - Governance Booklet, 2000 (Box 517, Folder 5)
    - Health Care Retreat, Agenda Book, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Historians Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box 443, Folder 24)
    - Historian's Handbook, undated (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Kemp, James P., Presidential Files
      - Incoming Correspondence, 1999 (Box 593, Folder 10-12)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1999 (Box 593, Folder 13-14)
    - Lichtenstein, Lawrence
      - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 389, Folder 6-7)
      - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 390, Folder 1-2)
    - Lockey, Richard, Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Binder 36-39)
    - Malkiel, Saul, Presidential Files, 1969-1971 (Box 443, Folder 25-26)
    - Meeting Agendas, 2005-2015 (Electronic \Series 01\, Electronic Meeting Agendas\)
    - Meeting Minutes
      - 1944 (Box 61, Folder 1-3)
      - 1944-1949 (Box 61, Volume 1)
      - 1950-1953 (Box 61, Volume 2)
      - 1954-1957 (Box 62, Volume 3)
      - 1958-1961 (Box 62, Volume 4)
      - 1962-1965 (Box 62, Volume 5)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 63, Volume 6)
      - 1968 (Box 63, Volume 7)
      - 1969 (Box 63, Volume 8)
      - 1970 (Box 63, Volume 9)
      - 1971 (Box 63, Volume 10)
      - 1972 (Box 64, Volume 11)
      - 1973 (Box 64, Volume 12)
      - 1974-1979 (Box 64, Folder 1-5)
      - 1980-1992 (Box 65, Folder 1-8)
      - 1993-1995 (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
      - Board of Directors
        - 1995 February & June (Box 597, Folder 12-13)
        - 1996 March, June, November (Box 597, Folder 14-16)
        - 1997 February, June, November (Box 597, Folder 17-18)
        - 1998 June, November (Box 597, Folder 19-20)
        - 2001-2015 (Electronic \Series 01\, Electronic Meeting Minutes\)
    - Meeting Transcript, 1947 December (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Middleton, Elliott, Jr., Presidential Files, 1972-1973 (Box 443, Folder 27)
    - Mini-Retreat, Agenda Book, 1995 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Norman, Philip, Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 390, Folder 3)
    - Orientation/Operations Manual
      - 1992-1995 (Box 66, Folder 5-9)
      - 1996 (Box 503, Folder 3)
      - 1997 (Box 543, Folder 57)
      - 1998/1999 (Box 597, Folder 21)
      - 1999/2000 (Box 503, Folder 4)
      - 2000/2001 (Box 543, Folder 56)
      - 2001/2002 (Box 503, Folder 5)
      - 2008 (Box 706, Folder 5)
    - Past Presidents, Meeting, Minutes, 1991 (Box 443, Folder 28)
    - Past Vice Presidents, 1973-1976 (Box 390, Folder 4)
    - Patterson, Roy
      - Historian files, 1973-1974 (Box 443, Folder 29)
      - Presidential Files, 1973-1977 (Box 443, Folder 30)
    - Pierson, William, Presidential Files
      - 1991 (Box 443, Folder 31)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 593, Folder 15)
    - Porter, William S., Attorney, Correspondence, 1984-1994 (Box 390, Folder 5-8)
    - Presidents, Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 443, Folder 32)
    - President's Handbook, undated (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - President's Symposium, 1988 (Box 390, Folder 9)
    - Rachelefsky, Gary, Presidential Files
      - Correspondence, December 1996-March 1998 (Box 534, Folder 38-49)
      - Telephone Calls, 1997-1998 (Box 533)
    - Reed, Charles
      - Historian's Files, 1969-1970 (Box 443, Folder 33)
      - Presidential Files, 1973 (Box 443, Folder 34)
    - Reference Manual
      - 2003-2004 (Box 540, Folder 52)
      - 2004-2005 (Box 534, Folder 8)
      - 2006-2007 (Box 597, Folder 22)
    - Reisman, Robert, Presidential Files, 1980-1981 (Box 443, Folder 35)
    - Retreat, Agenda Book
      - 1985 (Box 328, Folder 4-5)
      - 1986 (Box 378, Folder 4-7)
      - 1986 (Box 379, Folder 1)
      - 1990 (Box 379, Folder 2)
      - 1990 (Box 329, Folder 1-2)
    - Roy Patterson Lectureship, 1988 (Box 390, Folder 10)
    - Secretary's Files
      - 1973-1979 (Box 443, Folder 36)
      - 1980-1986 (Box 443, Folder 37)
    - Secretary's Handbook, 1976? (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Siegel, Sheldon
      - Presidential Files, 1973-1975 (Box 443, Folder 38)
      - Secretary Files, 1971-1973 (Box 443, Folder 39)
    - Strategic Planning Forum, 2003 (Box 494, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Planning Meeting
      - 1999 (Box 543, Folder 35)
      - 2000 (Box 540, Folder 55)
      - 2002 (Box 494, Folder 1)
      - Agenda and Supplemental Reference Material, January 2006 (Box 597, Folder 23-24)
    - Strategic Planning Retreat
      - 1990 (Box 685, Folder 7)
      - 1997 (Box 517, Folder 30)
      - 2000 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer's Files
      - 1964-1970 (Box 443, Folder 40)
      - 1975-1986 (Box 443, Folder 41)
    - van Arsdel, Paul, Secretary Files, 1963-1969 (Box 444, Folder 1-3)
    - VanMetre, Thomas, Presidential Files, 1978-1979 (Box 444, Folder 4)
    - Wasserman, Stephen, Presidential Files, 1998 (Box 593, Folder 16-19)
    - Zweiman, Burt, Presidential Files, 1994 (Box 593, Folder 20)
  - 2. Annual Meetings, 1944-2011
    This series contains materials from annual meetings, as well as pre- and post-meetings.
    - Abstract Submission Form and Instructions, 1979-1980, 1995-1996 (Box 526, Folder 33)
    - Abstracts
      - 1997-2011 (Electronic \Series 02\, Electronic Poster Abstracts\)
      - 2009 (Box 720, Folder 5)
      - Late Breaking, 2005 (Box 540, Folder 1)
    - Abstracts of Papers to be Presented During Scientific Sessions, 1974-1981 (Box 540, Folder 60-61)
    - Abstracts of Scientific Papers, 2007 (Box 677, Folder 2)
    - Academy Profile, 1989-1991 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Advertising Rate Schedule, 1995-1997 (Box 534, Folder 22)
    - Allergy, Asthma & Immunology Education and Research Trust Benefit Dinner, 2008 (Box 707, Folder 2)
    - Allied Health, Abstract and Travel Grant Submission Form and Instructions, 1998 (Box 526, Folder 31)
    - Allied Health
      - Course Tests, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Final Program, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Final Program, 1994-1998 (Box 461, Folder 6)
      - Preliminary Program, 1996, 1998 (Box 322, Folder 13)
      - Registration Booklet, 1990 (Box 375, Folder 1)
      - Registration Form, 1996, 1998 (Box 537, Folder 69)
    - Announcement, 2000-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - Awards, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Business Meeting
      - Agenda, 2009 (Box 720, Folder 6)
      - Presidential Addresses and Script, 1998 (Box 524, Folder 27)
      - Program
        - 1992-2000, 2002-2003 (Box 471, Folder 4)
        - 2004 (Box 513, Folder 6)
        - 2005, 2006, 2007 (Box 534, Folder 9)
    - Call for Abstracts/Papers, 1998, 2000-2005 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Cassette/CD Order Forms, 1990, 1992, 1995-2005 (Box 490, Folder 8)
    - Chrysalis Project, 2008 (Box 708, Folder 3)
    - City, Restaurant, and Tour Guides, 1980-2005 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
    - Commemorative Lectures and Awards, 1989-1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1948, 1950-1960 (Box 376, Folder 1-4)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 376, Folder 5-7)
    - Delegate Tracking Card, 1999-2000 (Box 375, Folder 2)
    - Disclosure Rosters, 1997-1998, 2001-2003, undated (Box 471, Folder 5)
    - Disclosure Statements: abstract presenters and speakers, 2006, 2007 (Box 674, Folder 2)
    - Education and Research Trust Benefit, 1993-2003, 2005 (Box 537, Folder 72)
    - Ethical Standards and Guidelines for Exhibitors, 1986-1987 (Box 444, Folder 5)
    - Evaluations
      - 1986-1991 (Box 57, Folder 7-11)
      - 1991-1993 (Box 58, Folder 1-6)
    - Evaluator Booklet, 2006 (Box 674, Folder 3)
    - Exhibit Guides
      - 1990-1991 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - 2000-2002, 2004-2005 (Box 444, Folder 6)
      - 2009 (Box 712)
    - Exhibitor Correspondence, 1960-1981 (Box 375, Folder 3-4)
    - Exhibitor's Prospectus
      - 1960 (Box 375, Folder 5)
      - 1967-1974 (Box 375, Folder 6)
      - 1975 (Box 321, Folder 7)
      - 1976-1981 (Box 375, Folder 7)
      - 1982-1989 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - 1990-1991 (Box 375, Folder 8)
      - 1994 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - 1995 (Box 524, Folder 11)
      - 1996-1998 (Box 444, Folder 7)
      - 1999-2001 (Box 321, Folder 8)
      - 2002 (Box 455, Folder 3)
      - 2003 (Box 494, Folder 6)
      - 2004 (Box 526, Folder 16)
      - 2005 (Box 540, Folder 42)
      - 2006 (Box 536, Folder 3)
      - 2007 (Box 674, Folder 8)
      - 2008 (Box 709, Folder 1)
    - Exhibitor Service Kit/Manual
      - 2000 (Box 321, Folder 6)
      - 2001 (Box 444, Folder 8)
      - 2004 (Box 526, Folder 18)
      - 2005 (Box 537, Folder 74)
      - 2006 (Box 674, Folder 4)
      - 2007 (Box 677, Folder 3)
    - Fisons Summary Service, 1990 (Box 493, Folder 4)
    - Handbook, 1944-1993 (Box 375, Folder 9-10)
    - Hostess Committee, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Hotel Reservation Card, 1976 (Box 537, Folder 94)
    - Hotel Reservation Forms, 2005 (Box 540, Folder 47)